Brazil is heading to a presidential runoff
after the top two finishers in Sunday's election
were unable to secure enough votes for an outright victory.
In combat, Luis Enazio Lula de Silva
will face Senator Flavio Bolsonaro,
the son of former President Jair Bolsonaro,
who is currently serving a 27-year sentence
for plotting a coup after losing the 2022 election.
The runoff is set for the 25th of October.
Brazil's presidential election
is heading into a second round, left his president Lula de Silva is fighting to extend
his time in office for the fourth non-consecutive term.
We have the second round, and the runoff is the moment of truth. It's time to show the
true picture of Brazil, because today is the Brazil we want. So starting tomorrow, we're
launching a new campaign.
Lula's rival Flavio Bolsonaro, the son of former president Shire Bolsonaro, is promising
a return to the right-wing policies of his family.
With nearly all votes counted Bolsonaro finished first, with 47 percent and Lula followed with